this video is going to tell you about
这部影片将告诉您
the revelation principle which is one of
启示原则是其中之一
the core ideas that makes mechanism
构成机制的核心思想
design possible so let's begin by
设计成为可能，所以让我们开始吧
finding out what the revelation
找出启示
principle says to us it says that any
原则对我们说，它说任何
social choice function that can be
社会选择功能可以是
implemented at all by any mechanism can
任何机制都可以实施
also be implemented by a truthful and
也可以由一个真实的
direct mechanism so let's recall what it
直接机制，让我们回想一下它是什么
means for a mechanism to be truthful and
意味着机制是真实的，
direct we say that a mechanism is direct
直接我们说一种机制是直接的
if it works by having all of the agents
如果通过让所有代理商起作用
simply make a single declaration you can
只需做出一个声明就可以
think of it as writing something down on
认为它是在写下一些东西
a piece of paper giving that to the
一张纸给那个
person who runs the mechanism and having
运行机制并具有
some decision be made an indirect
间接做出某些决定
mechanism in contrast might have a whole
相反，机制可能有一个整体
sequence of actions and information
行动和信息的顺序
revelation and subsequent actions that
启示和后续行动
depend on that information in Revelation
取决于启示录中的信息
multiple actions by different agents an
不同代理商的多项行动
indirect mechanism is essentially any
间接机制本质上是
sort of imperfect information Asia and
信息不完善的亚洲和
extensive form game
广泛的形式游戏
in contrast a direct mechanism is a
相反，直接机制是
simultaneous move Bayesian game so it's
同时移动贝叶斯游戏，所以
kind of like the sort of Bayesian
有点像贝叶斯
version of a normal form game now a
现在是普通形式游戏的一个版本
mechanism is truthful a direct mechanism
机制是真实的直接机制
is truthful if the equilibrium strategy
如果均衡策略是真实的
for every agent is when they have to
因为每个代理商都必须
write something down on that piece of
在那块东西上写下一些东西
paper is just to write down all of their
纸只是写下他们所有的
private information so simply to declare
私人信息，只需声明
what their type is so a truthful
他们的类型是如此真实
mechanism gives agents the very easiest
机制使代理商最容易
strategic problem that they can have
他们可能遇到的战略问题
agents are asked write me down something
代理商被要求写下我一些东西
on the piece of paper and the agents say
在纸上，代理商说
all right I'll tell you all of my
好吧，我会告诉你我所有的
secrets
机密
I'll just reveal everything to you on
我会告诉你一切
the piece of paper and you go off and
那张纸，你走了，
make a decision based on that and what
以此为基础做出决定
the revelation principle tells us kind
启示原理告诉我们
of surprisingly is that if I can
令人惊讶的是，如果我能
implement a social choice function in
实施社会选择功能
any complicated way I can also implement
任何我也可以实现的复杂方法
it in this very simple truthful direct
它以非常简单的真实直接
way so let's see how this works
这样，让我们​​看看它是如何工作的
I start with an arbitrary non truthful
我从任意非真实开始
mechanism which indeed may be
实际上可能是
direct so let me draw it here so what
直接，让我在这里画出来
happens is all of the agents have some
发生的是所有代理商都有一些
types because we're in a Bayesian game
类型，因为我们在贝叶斯游戏中
setting then they each take some
设置然后他们每个人都需要一些
strategy which is a function of their
策略是他们的功能
types that that tells them how to behave
告诉他们如何表现的类型
inside this mechanism and then some
在这个机制里面，然后一些
complicated thing happens in here maybe
也许这里发生了复杂的事情
we have information revelation there's
我们有信息启示
all kinds of maybe repetitions of agents
各种各样的代理重复
acting multiple times and then in the
表演多次，然后在
end eventually something happens the
最后最终发生了什么
mechanism decides an outcome well recall
机制决定结果的良好召回
that we can look at this whole thing as
我们可以将整个事情看作
being a game right in the end this is
最终成为游戏，这是
just a mapping from agents types and
只是来自代理类型的映射
strategies into some outcome that the
策略转化为某种结果
agents have utility for in the end and
代理商最终有效用
so I can think about an equilibrium of
所以我可以考虑一下
this game it's just some Bayesian game
这个游戏只是一些贝叶斯游戏
and so I can I can think about these
所以我可以考虑一下
asses all being in equilibrium with each
评估每个人都处于平衡状态
other and and that's exactly what I do
其他，这正是我所做的
when I talk about implementation if I
当我谈论实施时，如果我
say that the mechanism implements a
说该机制实现了
social choice function what I'm saying
社会选择功能我在说什么
is that in equilibrium the mapping from
是在平衡中
types to outcomes is the same as the
结果的类型与
mapping that would be chosen by the
映射将由
social choice function well here's the
社会选择功能很好，这是
punchline I want to show that I can make
我想证明的是，我可以做到
a new direct mechanism which is truthful
真实的新直接机制
and here's how I do it I take the
这就是我的做法
original mechanism and I kind of embed
原始机制，我有点嵌入
it in this new mechanism here so what I
它在这种新机制中，所以我
do is I say I'm gonna make a new
我是说我要做一个新的
mechanism whose action space is the same
作用空间相同的机制
as the type space so I'm gonna ask each
作为类型空间，所以我要问每个
of the agents tell me what your type is
代理商告诉我你的类型是
and of course the agents can do whatever
当然代理商可以做任何事情
they want they don't necessarily tell me
他们希望他们不一定告诉我
the truth but they tell me something and
事实是事实，但他们告诉我一些事情，
then I take that type that they've
然后我采用他们已经
declared so let me first of all give a
宣布，所以让我首先给一个
name to that so so I'll call that policy
为此命名，所以我将其称为政策
that agent I has for declaring his type
我要声明他的类型的那个经纪人
to me his strategy s prime I which is a
对我来说，他的策略是最重要的
function of his true type right so he
他的真正类型的功能正确，所以他
has he has some way of deciding based on
他有某种决定的依据吗
his type how to reveal something to me
他的类型如何向我揭示一些东西
so he'll come up with some type which is
所以他会想出一种
a func
一个功能
the real type that he has but maybe it's
他真正的类型，但也许是
not the truth maybe you'll tell me
不是事实，也许你会告诉我
something else I'll then take whatever
然后我会拿其他东西
he declares to me and I'll believe in
他向我宣告，我会相信
that that's his type and I'll stick that
那是他的类型，我会坚持下去
into s the strategy profile that we had
成为我们的战略概况
before which is our previous equilibrium
在此之前是我们之前的均衡
in the original mechanism so I'll take
用原来的机制，所以我会
that type all then figure out what
所有类型然后找出
strategy he would have played in the
他本该参加的策略
original mechanism if his type had been
如果他的类型是
what he declares to me and then I'll
他对我说的话，然后我会
simulate the original mechanism so if
模拟原始机制，如果
it's indirect inside this new mechanism
在这种新机制中是间接的
I'll kind of run a simulation of the new
我将对新产品进行模拟
mechanism I'll figure out what the
我会弄清楚
original mechanism would have done if
如果没有，原始机制会完成
everybody had played there they're
每个人都在那里玩过
declared types under the strategies that
在以下策略下声明类型
were previously in equilibrium and I'll
以前处于平衡状态，我会
figure out what the outcome is and I'll
弄清楚结果是什么，我会
make that the outcome of the new
使新的结果
mechanism well I want to claim that this
机制很好，我想声称这
new mechanism is truthful you can see
新机制是真实的，您可以看到
that it's direct its direct by
它是直接的
construction I want to claim that it's
建设我想声称这是
truthful and this should be kind of easy
真实，这应该很容易
to see it's truthful by exactly the same
完全一样地看到它是真实的
argument that s was in equilibrium so if
s处于平衡状态的论点
this mechanism isn't truthful that would
这种机制是不真实的
mean that s wasn't an equilibrium why
表示s不是一个平衡为什么
because it would mean if this mechanism
因为这意味着如果这种机制
isn't truthful then I want to I want to
是不真实的，那么我想要
declare some type here that isn't my
在这里声明不是我的类型
real type and if I'm declaring a my type
实型，如果我要声明我的类型
that isn't my real type that means I'm
那不是我的真实类型，这意味着我
changing the strategy that I would have
改变我的策略
played in the original mechanism I'm
发挥了我的原始机制
kind of what I would have preferred to
我本来希望的那种
also if I lie to the mechanism here I
如果我对这里的机制撒谎
would have preferred to lie to myself in
宁愿对自己说谎
the original mechanism so that I would
原始的机制，这样我就可以
effectively be playing a different
有效地发挥不同
strategy than I was playing before and
比我以前玩过的策略
of course the whole idea of an
当然，
equilibrium is that nobody can gain by
平衡是没有人可以通过
changing their strategy so if I wouldn't
改变他们的策略，所以如果我不愿意
have wanted to lie to myself in the
想要对自己撒谎
original mechanism to change my strategy
改变我策略的原始机制
nor would I want to lie to the mechanism
我也不想对机制撒谎
now because it's already playing a
现在，因为它已经在播放
strategy for me that's an equilibrium
对我来说，策略是均衡的
for the original mechanism and of course
对于原始机制，当然
that being the case it chooses the same
既然如此，它选择相同的
outcome since the original mechanism so
结局自原机制如此
kind of the the slogan for the
的口号是
revelation principle is that the agents
启示原则是代理商
don't need to lie in this new mechanism
不需要躺在这个新机制中
because the mechanism already lies for
因为机制已经存在
them right the mechanoid
他们正确的机械类
we feed their real types into the
我们将其真实类型输入
original mechanism instead we already
原来的机制，我们已经
apply this strategy of their types just
运用他们类型的策略
in the way that they were doing before
以他们以前的方式
and given that the mechanism is gonna do
鉴于该机制将
such a good job of lying for me just in
躺在我身上真是太好了
the way that I would have wanted to lie
我本想说谎的方式
there's no reason for me to lie again
我没有理由再说谎
right the mechanism is acting kind of as
正确，机制的作用就像
my proxy the mechanism is doing just
我的代理机制正在做
what I would like to do if only I tell
只要我告诉我我想做什么
it the right thing and so I should tell
这是正确的事情，所以我应该告诉
it the right thing that's the idea of
这是正确的想法
the revelation principle so there's one
启示原理，所以有一个
kind of technical concern too to mention
值得一提的技术问题
here which is that the set of equilibria
这就是均衡集
is not always the same in the original
原件并不总是一样
mechanism and the revelation mechanism
机制和启示机制
the revelation mechanism of course has
启示机制当然有
the original equilibrium we're
我们原来的平衡
interested in that's just what what I've
对那感兴趣的就是我所拥有的
shown you but it could actually
给你看，但实际上
introduce new equilibria which we don't
引入新的均衡，我们不会
like it's a bit of a technicality but
好像有点技术性，但是
it's worth telling you but but let me
值得告诉你，但让我
give you the high level point here which
给你高点在这里
is that the revelation principle really
启示的原则是
is important for mechanism design so so
对机构设计很重要，所以
why what is it good for well this kind
为什么这样对健康有好处
of three ways to see it it tells us the
看它的三种方式告诉我们
truthfulness is not a restrictive
真实性不是限制性的
assumption from the point of view of
从以下观点出发
what can be implemented likewise it
可以实现什么
shows us that direct mechanisms are not
向我们展示了直接机制不是
less powerful than indirect mechanisms
不如间接机制强大
which is a bit surprising because it
这有点令人惊讶，因为它
sort of feels like direct mechanisms are
感觉就像是直接机制
much more rich and complicated and they
更加丰富和复杂，他们
ought to be able to do more so this
应该能够做更多的事情
tells us no truthful and direct
告诉我们没有真实和直接的
mechanisms are enough if you can show
机制就足够了
that something is true for truthful and
真理是真实的，
direct mechanisms you've also shown that
直接机制你也证明了
it's true for all mechanisms and that's
所有机制都是如此，这就是
really important for analysis so if I
对于分析来说真的很重要，所以如果我
want to prove something about the space
想证明一些关于空间的东西
of all mechanisms in principle that
原则上所有机制
might seem really hard to do because I
似乎真的很难做，因为我
would have to grind through every
将不得不磨碎每一个
possible non truthful indirect mechanism
可能的非真实间接机制
seems like a hard set to think about so
似乎很难考虑
what the revelation principle tells me
启示原理告诉我什么
is that if I want to prove that you know
是如果我想证明你知道
mechanism exists with certain properties
存在具有某些属性的机制
or that some given mechanism is the best
或某种特定的机制是最好的
one that exists with certain properties
具有某些属性的一种
it's enough to show that it's the best
足以表明这是最好的
one among the set of truthful and direct
真实而直接的集合之一
mechanisms and that's a much more
机制，还有更多
manageable thing to do
可管理的事情
so really the revelation principle
所以真的是启示原则
in telling us that we can restrict
告诉我们我们可以限制
ourselves to truthful and direct
忠实而直接
mechanisms without loss of generality
不失一般性的机制
opens up the analysis of mechanisms and
打开机制分析并
we're gonna see in the future when we
我们将来会看到
prove things about mechanisms we always
证明关于我们始终存在的机制的事情
begin by saying without loss of
首先说而不失
generality let's restrict ourselves to
笼统地说，让我们局限于
truthful and direct mechanisms and that
真实而直接的机制
step is very important that's what makes
这是非常重要的一步
mechanism design feasible in practice
机制设计在实践中可行
and so that that's why we're telling you
所以这就是为什么我们告诉你
about this so early on this is a really
这么早就知道了
important foundational principle to
重要的基本原则
mechanism design
机制设计